I have raised this issue once again on SJVN. I would
like to know your opinion. Good strength is
visible in the stock. There
is a news quoting Reuters that the formation of JV between SJVN and GMR Energy has
got final approval and the joint venture for 900
MW hydro electric project has
got this approval. Please tell me what is your
view on SJVN. It is standing near 100 mark.
Buy at these levels. I think
its technical view is still negative. There is
bearish momentum. Right now the counter is
trading below all its exponential moving averages. So
till the counter does not sustain above 104 and 105 at higher levels, a
little caution should be
maintained. After crossing 105 in the counter,
a convexity will come towards buying and
if it crosses there, then we feel
that in the coming days, targets near about 116 to
118 can be seen.
Right now it is near a very crucial hurdle, so very
Aggressive trades should not be done in this with a buying bias.
Okay, today the results of ICICI Lombard are
coming. Please let me know
if you have any opinion before the results because currently
ICICI Lombard is trading towards the upper range of the day. Yes,
overall, a very
strong momentum is being seen right now
and it is expected that according to the
consolidation breakout that has come from right
near the cluster of moving averages, it is
expected that a bullish
momentum will continue from here to higher levels in the counter.
I think 2000 is the first stop,
but if the result is inflow, positive
flow continues and the market remains inline with it, then
I think as soon as there is a breakout above 2000,
higher movements of around 150 points can be
seen. So the
technical target is 2100 to 2150, but
after the results, we may see a strong momentum.